<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The homepage of Alex Bush</title>
    <link>https://alexbu.sh/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The homepage of Alex Bush</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexbu.sh/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The World Of Yesterday</title>
      <link>https://alexbu.sh/writing/reviews/TheWorldOfYesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbu.sh/writing/reviews/TheWorldOfYesterday/</guid>
      <description>I have never enjoyed an author&amp;rsquo;s company as much as I did whilst reading this book. Stefan Zweig&amp;rsquo;s personality infuses every page, and what a beautiful personality that is. His grand view of European liberalism and enthusiasm for artistic expression is the ideal antidote to the nationalism and political polarisation inherent in our current world. For me, the most riveting passages are those in which he describes meeting, and in some cases being closely acquainted with, what are now seen as some of the greatest artists, writers and composers of the twentieth century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tropic of Cancer</title>
      <link>https://alexbu.sh/writing/reviews/TropicOfCancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexbu.sh/writing/reviews/TropicOfCancer/</guid>
      <description>This book is not a pleasant book, nor is it a beautiful book. Arthur Miller describes, in great detail, the dirty, low, diseased and prostitute-obsessed world of Paris in the 1930s. His thesis is clear: if we are to celebrate and worship life, then we must seek out where life is the fullest, where life thrives in all the various ugly and festering corners. There is a beauty in every facet and variation of life, every form of existence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
